<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HobbyMart</string>
    <string name="company_name">By Laikapace Pvt Ltd</string>
    <string name="drone_desc">Explore list of best DIY drone kits best DIY drone kits. From Quadcopter DIY Combo Kit, Drone frame Kit, LiPo Battery, GPS module, Flight controller and BLDC Motors, Remote control we have it all!</string>
    <string name="company_info">Laikapace Pvt. Ltd. incorporated as a Private Limited Company on 09.08.2021 and is recognized by Ministry of MSME, Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA), Startup India, DPIIT:- Department for Promotion of Industry and Internal Trade. \n\nThe company is working in Aeronautical/Aerospace and Defence Industry and sector as self-certified. Currently the company is building a Fixed Wing UAV Laikapace 01 using solar power as supply energy resource capable of carrying Cameras and Other payloads according to requirement. The key point of our UAV Laikapace - 01 will be carrying higher amount of payload, Longer flight time, Green Energy as the power resource. Besides, soon we will be working on Remote Control Vehicles for Defence purpose and Electric Vehicle for common people.\n\nLaikapace Pvt. Ltd. is a Company of Aerospace, Aeronautics, Robotics enthusiasts who want to make changes in our society operating from Bangalore, Karnataka, India. We are using Green Energy for our UAV and Vehicles. Currently we are providing services like building quad-copter, 3D Printing, providing workshops, Internships and more. \n\nThe UAV will have the maximum Customizable possibility as per the customer requirement also the EV will be affordable for everyone.</string>
    <string name="plane_desc">Get Pre-build RC Plane with or without the battery. We built planes using high quality components ensured by our Team.</string>
    <string name="desc">

    </string>
    <string name="desc_1"><b>Purpose</b>
        Laikapace is committed to protecting any personal information that we may receive while you access our website. We believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive when you engage with us. This Privacy Policy is devised to help you feel more confident about the privacy and security of your personal details. \'You\' shall mean You, the User of the Website/ Application and ‘Yourself’ interpreted accordingly. \'We\' / \'Us\' means Laikapace and \'Our\' interpreted accordingly. \'Users\' means the Users of the Website/ application collectively and/or individually as the context allows.</string>
</resources>